

Mike Peters

Senior Digital Designer

- 678.858.6863
- info@mikepeters.io
- mikepeters.io

ABOUT

I'm a dedicated and highly motivated web professional with almost a decade of experience. I enjoy designing beautiful and functional user interfaces while also writing clean and efficient front-end code.

I believe good design is always in service of the user and it's my job to ensure that a project achieves both its business objectives and the needs of its users above all else.

SOCIAL

- Bē behance.net/mikeio
- in linkedin.com/in/mikepetersio/
- github.com/mikeio

EXPERIENCE

Force Marketing

2015 - 2017

Senior Digital Designer

Atlanta, Georgia

- Produced high-quality websites and applications, including user interfaces, sitemaps, wireframes and visual designs based on requirements.
- ▶ Developed mobile-friendly and responsive HTML products utilizing HTML, CSS and Javascript.
- Produced designs for interactive marketing materials, landing pages, e-mails campaigns and digital advertisements.
- Collaborated with various internal and external teams such as PHP and .Net developers as well as SEM and SEO teams.

Brightfire

2012 - 2015

Web Designer

Lawrenceville, Ga

- Worked directly with Live Nation and managed creative assets for multiple markets; specifically Live Nation Atlanta, Florida and the national market.
- Daily responsibilities included the creation of websites, applications, digital advertisements as well as print items such as posters, handbills, billboards and large format printed items.

RSVPATL 2010 - 2012

Graphic Designer

Atlanta, Ga

- Produced quality work in a fast-paced environment, meeting deadlines and client expectations for creativity and accuracy.
- Created branding for multiple clients including web sites, logo design, brochures, postcards, billboards and business cards.
- ▶ Helped clients revitalize their online presence using content management systems, event management software, social media platforms and digital advertising.



Mike Peters

Senior Digital Designer

- 678.858.6863
- mikepeters.io

ABOUT

I'm a dedicated and highly motivated web professional with almost a decade of experience. I enjoy designing beautiful and functional user interfaces while also writing clean and efficient front-end code.

I believe good design is always in service of the user and it's my job to ensure that a project achieves both its business objectives and the needs of its users above all else.

SOCIAL

- Bē behance.net/mikeio
- in linkedin.com/in/mikepetersio/
- github.com/mikeio

Neighborhood News

Junior Graphic Designer

2007- 2010Dacula, Ga

- Worked closely with the sales staff to create, modify and update advertisements in time to meet monthly advertising deadlines.
- I also worked directly with the editorial staff to design and build the monthly newspaper.

APPLICATIONS

- Adobe Photoshop
- Sketch
- ▶ Github

- Adobe Illustrator
- Sublime Text
- Codekit

- Adobe InDesign
- ▶ MAMP

SKILLS

- ▶ Fluent in HTML, CSS and preprocessor languages like SASS.
- Extensive knowledge of the Foundation and Bootstrap frameworks.
- Knowledge of version control systems such as Github and Bitbucket.
- Working knowledge of PHP and Javascript.

EDUCATION / AWARDS

- ▶ George Walton Academy High School Diploma
- US Achievement Academy
 All American Scholar Award